[MUSIC]
The upload file feature allows you to download a pack list file,
fill it out, and then upload it back into
Seller Central to provide your box content information.
This feature works for any type of shipment.
Enter the number of boxes in
your shipment and download the Excel-based template.
Open the file in a spreadsheet program.
For each box, enter the number of units per product,
expiration dates if applicable, and the box weight and dimensions.
After you're done entering the information, save the file.
Upload it back into Seller Central.
You do not need to convert the file into a different format.
You may instead download a text tab delimited version of the template.
If you prefer to work in that file format.